Okay, Hermes, how fast is
this thing going right now?
170? 200?
We're getting off of this thing! Emporio!
But when those rods came into my life
and I saw them for the first time,
I finally realized its importance.
It wasn't about the dude.
The moon landing was an
achievement for all humanity.
That day, we humans conquered
the moon and our spirits evolved.
What's truly significant is the
evolution of the human race!
You don't gotta worry about me.
I honestly don't even feel it.
Compared to all the shit I've
gone through to get to the priest,
this pain is nothing.
You crazy bitch!
If you're trying to test my spirit,
it's way stronger than yours!
I'm gonna finish you here!
Aw, shit!
Jolene! Aw, yeah!
A girl's alive!
He must be special since the priest
took away the disc with his memories.
And he decided to keep him
alive in that prison...
Weather forecast.
Because he happens to be the
priest's biological brother.
Let's go! To Orlando!
That's where we'll find him hiding, right?
Destiny is mine!
Thank you.
Thank you
so
much
for joining us.
That's it, though.
I don't want to be the one.
It's not that the one.
I'm not that the one.
I'm not my friend.
Hurry!
Get surgery room 3 prepared.
We've got an eight-year-old
boy in critical condition.
It's okay. It'll be okay.
Hey, Jolene.
You said this is where
the priest was hiding.
But this is a fucking hospital?
He's here.
I don't know why, but he's
definitely waiting for us inside.
We're going to put an end to this here.
Emporio.
I need a favor.
This is important.
I want you to take my father's
disc and deliver it for me.
If you call this number, the
Speedwagon Foundation will come get it.
I want to go in with you! I know.
But before that, I need you to
make sure the disc gets delivered.
It's all up to you.
By now, the priest should sense
that I'm getting closer to him.
I don't want to be separated
from you right now either.
But it's necessary.
Keep in touch with this cell
phone I took off Rikiel.
Sorry to bother you,
but I'd like to hear your opinion
on something I'm unsure of,
particularly this dish.
Take a bite if you would.
I want you to taste test it for me.
Versus...
One bite is enough.
After you eat it, tell me
what ingredients are inside.
If there's shellfish, I can't eat it.
I'm allergic, so I would get quite sick.
This is whitefish.
Most likely, flounder.
It has been paired with this flan, a
delectable pudding mixed with asparagus,
and mashed up crab meat inside.
I detect no shellfish.
Incredible.
But hold on a second.
May I have another small bite, but this
time with a little dab of sauce on the side?
There's a faint scent from the sauce.
Judging by the fishy aroma, I suspect
it's scallop paste mixed with cream.
How unfortunate?
Just as I thought, there are
scallops inside the sauce!
Is your shoe size 27 centimeters?
Pardon me, but could
you stand for a moment?
Be careful not to open up
the bullet wound on your leg.
Slowly now.
You're about 181 centimeters tall? Yes.
And you weigh precisely 72 kilograms?
Are your clothes size 52?
And do you tighten your watch
belt on the second hole?
Yes.
How interesting?
Though I'm unable to enjoy this fine meal.
I'm quite impressed by your ability to
pick out the scallop from the sauce.
It would appear we have
a similar sense of taste.
Interesting indeed.
Tell me, Father Poochie,
what are you trying to say?
You're aware I haven't
seen my own ability yet?
And plus, I can sense someone
quickly approaching our location.
I want to help in any way I can.
What should I do?
Hmm.
That can't be helped.
In fact, their arrival might
actually prove useful to me.
Oh, Mike.
Your son's going to be fine.
He's really close now.
He's here somewhere.
If you're still unable
to see your ability,
then there's nothing
else that can be done.
Don't struggle against things
beyond your understanding.
Let the power take its own course.
If we are going to make it to heaven,
You must ally yourself with the
power that lies dormant within you.
And besides, there's a chance Jolene
might overlook this room entirely.
Nevertheless,
I decided to order this dish because they
told me there'd be no shellfish inside.
If you'd like, you may eat it yourself.
Father Pooji.
I, uh, I...
I...
I was...
Look at me!
I was shot to death!
It was a lot of fun going
for a ride in the ambulance,
but it was ruined because
my daddy doesn't like me.
My daddy's the one who shot me!
He was trying to kill me!
Honey! Honey!
Honey, what happened?
Someone was shot!
Oh, God! Why?
Why did you have to take it?
No! No!
What the hell?
This hospital room is a mess.
That priest must have been in here.
But now, where the fuck is he hiding?
Whatever's going on, I
think it's safe to assume?
That the new enemy that's been
hanging around the priest.
is the cause of all this.
Although, that gunshot didn't
exactly feel like a stand attack.
It's more like somebody
fired a real bullet.
And the poor bastard that got shot.
Who even is that guy?
Why would he be the one to get hit?
I mean, looking at him, he seems
to be just a random ordinary dude.
I need you to hurry and
evacuate everyone on this floor.
Now! Yes, sir!
Hey, that goes for you two as well!
Hurry up and evacuate!
I'm going to go call the police!
That's right.
I remember that man now.
He's the parent of that
kid who was brought in
by the ambulance when we
first got to this place.
Maybe it was a test shot. Huh?
I have no idea what kind
of ability it could be,
but if it's someone who just
had their powers awakened,
they would need to give it a test
drive and try it out on somebody first.
The priest is moving right now.
Somewhere down there.
That bastard's inside the hole.
I can sense him getting
further away from here.
Come on, Jolene.
Don't just throw yourself
into the hole like an idiot.
Sorry, but I'm against you on this one.
Anybody could see it's an obvious trap.
Don't even go near the thing until we can
find a clear connection between this deep,
dark abyss and the man who
got shot up in the hallway.
Whoever dug this hole started tunneling
to the side when they got deep enough.
I can't see beyond that.
The person that's accompanying Father
Poochie right now goes by the name Versus.
25, male.
Listen to me, Jolene.
I said it before and I'll say it again.
I ain't going down in this damn hole.
Let's just wait for him to climb out.
Or we gotta find a way to
drag him out like rabbits.
I'm already well aware that
this hole is an obvious trap.
I'm not stupid.
But what happens if the priest is
planning to hole himself up down
there for three more days while
he waits for the new moon to come?
No.
Given how capable he is,
I bet Poochie and his accomplice plan to
escape all the way to
Cape Canaveral like this.
In three days,
that man's going to develop
some new ability that
will help him attain his
absurd idea of heaven.
But for now, all he has is Pale Snake,
which merely allows him to
control the memories of others.
This is our chance if we
strike him now we can win
We can't avoid it anymore if
we want to end this for good.
We might have to kill the priest
Hold on to this huh?
Don't let go no matter what
Hey, Joanne, what do
you think you're doing?
I'm coming with you
If we both go who's gonna stay
here to help pull me back up?
Take my rope and wrap it around your body
if I need help I'll signal You got it?
Pull me out of here, whatever it takes.
She is crazy.
But still though, Jolene,
if you keep pulling this
thread out of your body,
just how far can you go
before you run out of slack?
Jolene!
Jolene! Hey!
Why aren't you answering me? Jolene!
Where...am I?
2005?!
What the...
Hey, look.
She came all this way
dragging her rope behind her.
I'll go cut it.
Fuck, not good.
Where am I?
Hermes, hey! Can you hear me?
Things are bad!
Start pulling me up! Hurry!
Now, Hermes!
I'm in trouble.
Please, get me out of here!
They're gonna cut the rope!
Come on, Hermes!
What are you waiting for?
Hurry, please!
Hermes!
Pull me out of the fucking hole!
I know you can hear me!
Goddammit, what the ever-living
fuck is going on down there?
and she couldn't have really
gone that far into the hole!
Go, Hermes! Keep pulling!
You're gonna have to pull me up even more!
I welcome you.
Even though you've come uninvited
and haven't greeted me, you may stay.
You chose to come into my hole
of your own volition. However,
I must insist the entirety of this tightly
pulled rope comes in with you as well.
Stone Ocean!
Hey Versus, will you be alright?
Compared to you who has recently
developed a new stand ability,
Jolene Kujo has undergone intense training
through her experiences in prison.
She is much more accustomed
to all-out battle.
It's not surprising that she would steal a
pen from one of the
passengers on the plane.
Do not pursue Jolene any further.
You have done enough already, versus.
If Jolene wants to escape
from this hole, then so be it.
She won't attempt to
come back inside again.
At least not for a while.
For now, all we can do is wait patiently.
We'll need to stay here
for three more days.
Can you hear me up there, Hermes?
I can see a light now!
I must be getting close to you!
Pull me up even harder,
okay? Yeah! Jolene!
I can hear you!
And I'm starting to be able to see you!
Are you okay?
What the hell is down in this deep hole?
The enemy is staring
right at me as we speak!
Also, I could see the priest.
He's in here, too.
We have to come up with another
way for us to get down here again.
It would have been over
if they'd cut this rope.
Tell me something I want to know.
Hey, come on now, Hermes.
How are you feeling?
I'm just a little curious.
I really want to know.
How did it feel to get revenge on the
son of a bitch who murdered your sister?
Did you get some sort of
sick satisfaction out of
burring me alive in that sewer
pipe you called an improv,
Goffin?
It's Sports Maximum!
Hey!
What's going on, Hermes?
What are you doing up there?
Sorry, Jolene!
The ground has a long memory of
everything that happens upon it.
Sort of like a tape recorder, or
even much like a digital camera.
For example,
it remembers that boy who was shot dead by
his own father when he
fell onto the ground.
Shit, where the hell are you?
It even remembers the
gangster who was buried
alive in a sewer pipe
and drowned to death.
The Earth's memory is so powerful that it
can even recall every single one of the
passengers who met their demise on a plane
that fell to the ground in July of 2005,
six years ago.
Hermes, hey!
What the hell are you doing up there?
Come on, Hermes! Stop! Let go of me!
I'm here thanks to versus stand ability
see netherworld uncovers all the
folks who met the ground when they
perished and excavates their memories
Asshole!
Joey!
Excuse me, ladies. Welcome
aboard. Unfortunately,
this plane is expected
to lose control and crash
into the ground at approximately
2133 on July Saudi, 2005.
We ask that you please turn
off all electronic devices,
and make sure that your seatbelt is
securely fastened around your lower waist.
I suggest you heed that warning,
or you'll end up like the man who
was sitting in the seat behind me.
His head was lodged straight
into my stomach on impact.
What? Ain't no way! Dammit!
Where's the entrance?
Start looking, Hermes!
Help me find it!
Wait, what even is this place?
Is this a hallucination, Jolene?
It should be on the ceiling.
Look for the place we came in from.
Everything in this fucking
plane feels so real, though.
We need to find the way out of here now.
Before you fell down, was there anyone
coming to check the room above the hall?
There was a panic in the halls
after that boy's dad was shot.
The police had to have shown up.
Did you see anyone?
No, I have no clue. Besides,
even if the cops came, they
wouldn't be able to hear us calling,
just like I couldn't hear
you up there earlier.
How's this plane down here anyway?
I didn't see anything like this when I
was waiting for you to come out the hall.
Excuse me, miss, please refrain
from punching the ceiling.
If you would, kindly take
your seat and wait quietly.
This plane will be crashing
in less than three minutes.
Okay, then let us see the pilot!
We gotta make him land
this plane immediately!
Now hurry up, lady, and
take us to the cockpit!
No point.
We weren't able to land the plane safely.
That's the reason why we crashed!
Unfortunately for us, we all burned
to death when the plane crash landed.
It exploded and That was when my body
um excuse me sir did you not hear me
when I told everyone to turn off of all
of their electronic devices earlier?
Could it be?
I think I remember this.
It was flight number 2882 to Dallas.
Around six or seven years ago, it
crashed somewhere near Orlando.
We're dealing with ghosts here.
No, we're memories.
That's all.
Remnants of memories that
were recorded by the Earth.
Are you trying to tell me we're
actually gonna crash in this thing?
Can you not make this plane
crash happen any faster?
I've been sensing weather forecasts
getting closer to our position.
It appears that he is drawing
ever closer toward this hospital.
I swear to God, if you don't shut the fuck
up already and stop confusing me, Huh.
Were you speaking to me?
Netherworld's ability is to
excavate memories from the ground.
And this plane is set to crash
specifically at 2133 on the dot.
Also,
try not to forget that
I've capitalized on this
opportunity and managed to pull
Ermes into my hole as well.
I have done this all for you, Father.
Now just leave it to me.
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place
other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny?
I'm thinking
about all the
things I'd like
to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer.
A distant dreamer.
Dreaming far away.
From today!
Thank you.